let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Talent", "answer": "Gabe", "options": ["Gabe", "Ablauf", "Behalter", "Seitew\u00e4rts"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Frequently", "answer": "H\u00e4ufig", "options": ["Ahnung", "Leitung", "Urteil", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Container", "answer": "Behalter", "options": ["Abfall", "Behalter", "bedinungen", "Gewitter"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "answer": "knapp", "options": ["Vertrag", "Vierecke", "knapp", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "answer": "Mangel", "options": ["Gabe", "Wesentlich", "Angabe", "Mangel"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Assumption", "answer": "Ahnung", "options": ["Vertrag", "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Seitew\u00e4rts", "Ahnung"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "Judgement", "answer": "Urteil", "options": ["Ablauf", "Betrieb", "Urteil", "Hinweise"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "process", "answer": "Verlauf", "options": ["kreis", "Ahnung", "H\u00e4ufig", "Verlauf"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Task", "answer": "Aufgabe", "options": ["Anzug", "Vorw\u00e4rts", "Aufgabe", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Wastage", "answer": "Abfall", "options": ["Wesentlich", "Dreieck", "Behalter", "Abfall"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "circle", "answer": "kreis", "options": ["kreis", "Dreieck", "H\u00e4ufig", "Behalter"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "expired", "answer": "Ablauf", "options": ["Ablauf", "Geb\u00e4ude", "bedinungen", "Behalter"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Script", "answer": "Schrifft", "options": ["Schrifft", "Vorw\u00e4rts", "Leitung", "knapp"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Backward", "answer": "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "options": ["Aufgabe", "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Dreieck", "Anzug"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Rectangular", "answer": "Vierecke", "options": ["Behalter", "Vierecke", "knapp", "Ahnung"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "Operation,", "answer": "Betrieb", "options": ["Ablauf", "Betrieb", "Angabe", "Vertrag"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Suit, Costume", "answer": "Anzug", "options": ["Anzug", "Dreieck", "Gabe", "knapp"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Leadership, Conduct", "answer": "Leitung", "options": ["Urteil", "Leitung", "Schrifft", "Anzug"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "answer": "Gewitter", "options": ["Gewitter", "Betrieb", "Vertrag", "Ruckw\u00e4rts"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Triangle", "answer": "Dreieck", "options": ["Angabe", "Geb\u00e4ude", "Dreieck", "Betrieb"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "forward", "answer": "Vorw\u00e4rts", "options": ["Vorw\u00e4rts", "Aufgabe", "Betrieb", "Mangel"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Crucial", "answer": "Wesentlich", "options": ["Behalter", "Wesentlich", "Ablauf", "knapp"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "buildings", "answer": "Geb\u00e4ude", "options": ["Geb\u00e4ude", "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Mangel", "Wesentlich"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Sideways", "answer": "Seitew\u00e4rts", "options": ["Seitew\u00e4rts", "Vierecke", "Ahnung", "Vorw\u00e4rts"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Contract", "answer": "Vertrag", "options": ["Vierecke", "Vertrag", "kreis", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "answer": "Angabe", "options": ["Gewitter", "Vorw\u00e4rts", "Anzug", "Angabe"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "answer": "Hinweise", "options": ["Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Aufgabe", "Abfall", "Hinweise"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "answer": "bedinungen", "options": ["Aufgabe", "Abfall", "knapp", "bedinungen"]}];